Mss.B.M891
American Philosophical Society
- Reproductions, 18th and 19th century; 0.25 ln. ft.
  - Letters, various correspondents, 19th century; Photostats.; Muhlenberg, Peter, 1746-1807
  - Letters, various correspondents, Photostats.; Muhlenberg, William Augustus, 1796-1877